<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 22:02:54 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Geography</title>
      <link>/post/geography/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 22:02:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/geography/</guid>
      <description>Forge world Malleaton is located in the REDACTED system. This used to be a vibrant system with mining words, population centres and worlds wholly dedicated to research. After the events of REDACTED the system looks wholly different.
The main forge world &amp;ldquo;planet&amp;rdquo; Maelleaton has been broken up into four pieces. Three main asteroids all connected with the frozen core, the frozen core &amp;ldquo;Maelleaton Alpha&amp;rdquo; is mostly used for mining and has some temples recognising the past of the system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organizational structure</title>
      <link>/post/government/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 22:02:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/government/</guid>
      <description>The main body of this forgeworld is the Ruling council. It is located on a space station name the fabricator general orbiting the core of the broken planet. The council is made of three Magi, one from a Magos Biologis, Magos Enginseer and Magos Dominus. Each representing one of the main bodies from the planet.
This forge worlds owes it allegiance to Forge world Lucius</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colours</title>
      <link>/post/colours/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/colours/</guid>
      <description>Deep in the archives of the forge world there are references to ancient colour names. These colours are holy and shall enver be renamed. Here are some data fragments of the archive:
Piece Colour Cloak Base Phoenician purple Metal Leadbelchers (or special runefang steel) Wood Mornfang brown Bronze weapon bronze Paper Morghast bone + corax white; agrax earthshade Energy goblin green (game color) Blue energy electric blue </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History</title>
      <link>/post/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/history/</guid>
      <description>This forge world was rediscover during the horus heresy. The first part of the Impirium that they came into contact with was the Raven Guard. This was a part of the Raven Guard that was sent away from the rest of the legion, the forge world quickly accepted their place in the Impirium and tried to find contact with the rest of the mechanicum. Forge world Lucius was the first to send a Ark Mechanicus ship to establish a relationship and share the current technology.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
